Contact

avi210892@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/avizaguri-41869b11b (LinkedIn) github.com/aviz92 (Other)

Top Skills

Project Management
Python (Programming Language)
Software Design Patterns

Languages

Hebrew

English

Certifications

CCNA Routing and Switching Robot FrameWork Python CCNP Routing and Switching

Avi Zaguri

Technical Leader Python developer at Airspan Networks Israel

Summary

Avi Zaguri, a B.Sc. Electrical Engineer and an M.Sc. System Engineer.

As part of my master's degree, I conducted a research project called "Evaluation of System Modeling Tools and Methods for Industrial Applicability". As part of the research, collaboration was conducted with Systematix on a new Matlab tool called "System Composer" - a new simulation tool for systems engineers.

- * This project won the title of "commendable" as part of the master's degree.
- * Link to Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oIQI3nzUyUU
- * An article on the HIT website: https://www.hit.ac.il/mot/ news_events/complex_system_modeling

I'm an experienced software developer (technical leader), during my work I use libraries and complex tools, develop applications and automation infrastructures while characterizing, and designing the systems.

I'm an experienced network engineer and have extensive experience working in the networking industry. with capabilities as far as to design, definition, configure, building security architecture solutions, maintenance of complex IT system infrastructures, and high-performance computing.

Also, I have experience with network protocols of LTE, network products LTE (SGW, EPC, Security GW, etc..), and LTE hardware (eNBs).

During my various jobs, I have gained much knowledge and developed a deep understanding of the business environment, demonstrated high management capabilities, and the ability to work with a multitude of interfaces - international companies, contractors, and vendors.

Also, I working with many tools for analysis of complex information such as Wireshark, motion injection tools (such as Spirent, IxLoad, etc..), and Independent developments applications (developing by Python)

Experience

Airspan Networks
Technical leader Python developer
2018 - Present (3 years)

- Technical leader Python developer
- Characterization, design, definition of work processes, and development of organizational applications
- Full management of Python infrastructure
- Optimizing employee work by developing unique tests application and log analyses
- Management of processes, assimilation, and upgrading of systems from the moment of their acceptance/implementation of the change to their operationalization (including integration)
- Writing procedures LTE network while analyzing the network and drawing conclusions
- Development according to design patterns such as Abstract Factory,
 Singleton, Adapter, Observer, Strategy, and etc.
- Knowledge and experience with OOP and libraries such as paramiko, pandas, numpy, tkinter, jira, elasticsearch, plotly, matplotlib, logging, robotframework, and etc.
- Knowledge and experience with Django framework
- Knowledge and experience with Robot framework
- Work with databases such as PostgreSQL
- Work with REST API such as Jira, Confluence and etc.
- Work with Github

Additional talents:

- Knowledge and experience with analysis software such as Wireshark, and etc.
- Understanding Windows / Linux workspaces. Scripting (Windows / Linux)
- Knowledge and experience with many motion injection tools such as Spirent, IxLoad, and etc.

• Experience with network protocols of LTE, network products LTE (SGW, EPC, Security GW, etc..), and LTE hardware (eNBs)

As part of my work, I developed central applications, for example:

- Automated and optimized, collecting and analyzing data on all the hardware in the company and the customers, opening objects in Jira, and defects to the relevant teams.
- Complete full automation system for automation testing.
 The system is based on Python, Django framework, Robot framework, and Jenkins.

The system actually replaces all the automation that exists in the company.

Rafael Advanced Defense Systems - Career Network Engineer - Technical leader 2017 - 2018 (1 year)

Israel

- Network engineer Technical leader
- Full management of the Cisco network infrastructure including Switches & Routers (1800, 2800, 2900, 3900, C2960, C3750, 4500).
- Design, characterization, and integration of new architectures in the organization, analysis, and improvement of the existing architectures in the organization.
- Writing procedures in all areas of the network, computing, and information security, while analyzing the network and drawing conclusions.
- Management of processes of assimilation and upgrading of systems from the moment of their acceptance/implementation of the change to their operationalization (including integration).
- Optimizing network performance, from communications equipment, computing, F.W infrastructure, and more.
- Familiar with network protocol: VLAN, ACL, STP, Port-channel, HSRP, OSPF, EIGRP.
- Familiarity and maintenance of Check Point's FW (including command line).

Additional talents:

- Knowledge and experience with software such as Wireshark, SCCM.
- Understanding Win / Linux workspaces. Scripting if necessary (Win / Linux).

IAF - Israeli Air Force Network Engineer 2012 - 2017 (5 years)

- Setup, operation and maintenance of switch & router, including support and troubleshooting of complex communication problems.
- Guiding and redesigning the network to meet the growing demand from customers and for new projects.
- Extensive experience in setting up communication sites from scratch to full operation of communications and computer systems.
- Work and manage against the Active Directory and GPO of the organization, including technical support for the entire organization.
- Information security and anti-virus management (including the EPO server).
- Knowledge and experience with monitoring systems such as Cloud, Centerity and military control systems.

Additional talents:

- Command, and training new employees for communications professionals and network administrators.
- Extensive experience in team work, management and prioritization of tasks, work under great pressure and at irregular hours 24/7.
- Understanding Win / Linux workspaces. Scripting if necessary (Win / Linux).
- Knowledge in programming languages: C, Assembler, VHDL, MATLAB.

Education

Holon Institute of Technology

M.Sc., System Engineering · (2018 - 2020)

Holon Institute of Technology

B.Sc, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (2014 - 2018)

Amal Technology College

Practical Engineer, Electronics and Computers · (2010 - 2012)